boxycharm.com 2019-11-11

# Privacy Policy - BOXYCHARM: The Best Monthly Beauty and Makeup Box Subscription

Last Modified: July  2, 2019 

Boxy Charm Inc. (collectively with its affiliates and subsidiaries 

“Company”  or  “We”  or  “Us” ) the operator of this web site ( www.boxycharm.com ) (also known as the “Website”), respects your privacy and is committed to protecting and preserving it through our compliance with this Privacy Policy (as used herein “Policy”).

This Policy (together with our Terms and Conditions and any other documents referred to in it) describes the Personal Information that We collect from you, or that you provide on the Website, and how, when, and why that information may be used by Us or disclosed by Us. This Policy applies to information gathered on this Website, through the Company’s mobile application, and to communications between you and this Website. This Policy does not apply to information We collect through any other means, or to information collected on any other web site other than the Website, including any affiliate or third-party site or by any third-party application that may link to or be accessible from the Website.

Please read the following Policy carefully to understand our policies and practices regarding your Personal Information and how We will treat it. 

THIS POLICY DOES NOT APPLY TO OTHER WEB SITES WHICH MAY BE LINKED TO THE WEBSITE. YOU AGREE THAT YOUR USE OF THIS WEBSITE SIGNIFIES YOUR ASSET TO THE TERMS OF THIS PRIVACY POLICY. IF YOU DO NOT AGREE TO BE BOUND TO THE TERMS OF THIS PRIVACY POLICY, YOU ARE NOT AUTHORIZED TO USE THIS WEBSITE AND SHOULD DISCONTINUE YOUR USE AND ACCESS OF THIS WEBSITE IMMEDIATELY.

## Information We Collect About You

We collect several types of information from and about users of our Website, including:

  * Information you provide to Us, known as Personal Information, described below;
  * Information about you and your means of accessing the Website that does not individually identify you, including Usage Details described below, which We obtain as you access the Website. 
  * Information We receive from third parties, for example, our business partners.

## Personal Information (i.e. Information You Provide to Us)

We may collect and use the following information that you provide to Us:

  * Information that you provide by filling in forms on our Website. This includes your name, e-mail address, shipping address, telephone number, and credit card information, along with other personal information about yourself (“Personal Information”). This Personal Information is collected at the time of registering to use our Website, subscribing to our service, purchasing goods and/or services from Us, making returns with Us, subscribing to email updates from Us, interacting with our mobile site, or social media sites, participating in any contests or promotions offered by Us, posting material or requesting further service from Us, or through communications with Us related to any comments, questions or concerns you may have about Us. We may also ask you for information when you enter a contest or promotion sponsored by Us, and when you report a problem with our Website.
  * Records and copies of your correspondence (including e-mail addresses), if you contact Us.
  * Your responses to surveys that We might ask you to complete, although you are not required to respond to them.
  * Details of transactions you carry out through the Website and of the fulfilment of your orders. You may be required to provide financial information before placing an order through the Website.
  * All credit card information provided to Us is maintained in a secure and safe environment.
  * We will use Personal Information to process and fulfill your orders, to provide you with timely updates as to the status of your orders, to support your experience using the Website, and to otherwise provide you with the products and services you request from Us. We may use this Personal Information to provide you with a personalized profile of your shopping history, to notify you about new services and programs available from Us, or to send you offers or information related to the Website.
  * Certain trusted third parties may access your Personal Information, including third parties that host this Website, third parties used to send emails for Us, and third parties used to assist in the fulfillment of your orders or requests for services. 
  * Unless you expressly consent otherwise, your Personal Information will only be disclosed to Us, our affiliates, technical consultants and staff, third party auditors and other third parties who facilitate the delivery of the Website and or provide you with products and services, and We agree to require them to agree to be bound to this Policy.

We will never sell, rent, or share your Personal Information, including your email address, provided to Us without your express consent.

## Usage Details, IP Addresses, Cookies and Other Technologies

As you navigate through and interact with our Website, We may automatically collect certain information about your equipment, browsing actions and patterns. The information We collect automatically helps us to improve our Website and to deliver a better and more personalized service, including by enabling Us to:

  * Estimate our audience size and usage patterns.
  * Store information about your preferences, allowing Us to customize our Website according to your individual interests.
  * Speed up your searches.
  * Recognize you when you return to our Website.
  * Comply with lawful requests from third parties.

The technologies we use for this automatic data collection may include:

  * Cookies.   We may obtain information about your general internet usage by using cookies. A cookie is a small file passed from our Website to your computer that is stored on the hard drive of your computer. Cookies allow the Website to understand your use of the Website. Use of cookies help Us to improve our Website and to deliver a better and more personalized service by enabling Us to:

  * Estimate our audience size and usage patterns.
  * Store information about your preferences, allowing Us to customize our Website according to your individual interests.
  * Speed up your searches.
  * Recognize you when you return to our Website. 
  * Track your status

  * Web Beacons .  Our Website and the emails We send may contain small electronic files known as web beacons (also known as clear gifs or single pixel gifs) that permit the Company, for example, to count users who have visited those pages or opened an email, and to gather other related Website Statistics (for example, recording the popularity of certain Website content and verifying the integrity of systems and servers We operate).
  * Usage Details and IP Addresses.   We may also collect details of your visits to our Website, including, but not limited to, traffic data, location data, logs and other communication data, whether this is required for our own billing purposes or otherwise, and the resources that you access, as well as frequency of visits, cookies, web beacons, information about your computer and internet connection, including your IP address, operating system and browser type (“Usage Details”). We aggregate that data (“Aggregated Data”) in a manner that does not allow for the identification of any specific individual Website visitor.  This Aggregated Data is used for system administration, and is shared with advertisers. This is statistical data about our users' equipment, browsing actions and patterns, and does not identify any individual Website visitor.
  * Third-Party Advertiser Use of Cookies and Other Tracking Technologies.  Some advertisements on the Website are served by third-party advertising companies. Our advertisers may also use cookies alone or in conjunction with web beacons or other tracking technologies to collect information about our users. We do not control third-party advertisers' cookies or how they may be used, or how any data obtained by those third party advertisers may be protected. If you have any questions about an advertisement, you should contact the responsible advertiser directly.
  * Email data:  We may receive information from you when you open emails sent by Us. If you do not want to receive email from Us, please use the information at the bottom of the email sent to you to unsubscribe and we will promptly remove you from our mailing lists.

## Browser Do Not Track Signals

Although our Website currently does not have a mechanism to recognize the various web browser Do Not Track signals, We do offer our customers choices to manage their preferences that are provided in this Policy. To learn more about browser tracking signals and Do Not Track please visit http://www.allaboutdnt.org/.

User Content   
You are responsible for any content, including Personal Information, that you contribute to be published or displayed (hereinafter, “Posted”) on the Website, on any forums or discussion threads provided to users of the Website, whether restricted in access to a limited group of Website users or made public to all Website users, or transmitted to other users of the Website (collectively, “User Content.”) Your User Content is Posted on and transmitted to other users of the Website at your own risk. 

Although We take security seriously, please be aware that no security measures are perfect or impenetrable. Additionally, We cannot control the actions of other users of the Website with whom you may choose to share your User Content. Therefore, We cannot and do not guarantee that your User Content will not be viewed by unauthorized persons. We are not responsible for circumvention of any privacy settings or security measures contained on the Website.

 You understand and acknowledge that, even after removal, copies of your User Content may remain viewable in cached and archived pages, or might have been copied or stored by other Website users. Proper access and use of information provided on the Website, including User Content is governed by our  Terms and Conditions  and known or suspected violations should be reported via email at:  [[email protected]](https://web.archive.org/cdn-cgi/l/email-protection) .

## User Forums. 

The Company may provide its users with the ability to interact among themselves via user forums or discussion threads that allow users of the Website to share information or exchange products among other users. However, all users communicate information and otherwise use those forums or discussion threads at their own risk. The Company has no liability or responsibility for any agreements or contracts made between users of the Website over the forums or message threads, and bears no responsibility or liability for the result of any interactions between users of the Website conducted on the user forums or message threads. 

## Social Networking.

We may allow you to enable or log in to the Website or access any of the features, functionalities, products or services of the Website via social networking services like, for example, Facebook (“Social Networking Service(s)”). To use these features, you may be required to log into the relevant Social Networking Service. We will collect relevant information necessary to enable Us and the Website to access that Social Networking Service and your User Information contained within or held by that Social Networking Service. As part of our Website’s integration with Social Networking Services, the Social Networking Service would provide Us with access to certain information that you have provided to that Social Networking Service, and We would use, store, and disclose such information in accordance with this Privacy Policy.  However, please remember that the manner in which Social Networking Services use, store and disclose your information is governed by the specific policies of those third parties and We shall have no responsibility or liability for the privacy practices or other actions of any Social Networking Services that may be enabled through the Website or provide access to the Website.

You may have the option of posting your Boxy Charm activities to Social Networking Services. You acknowledge that if you choose to use this feature, your friends, followers, subscribers or other third parties on those Social Networking Services you have enabled may be able to view such activity. 

## How We Use Your Information

We use information that We collect about you or that you provide to Us, including Personal Information, in the following ways:

  * To present our Website and its contents in a suitable and effective manner for you and for your computer.
  * To provide you with information, products or services that you request from Us.
  * To carry out our obligations and enforce our rights arising from any contracts entered into between you and Us.
  * To notify you about changes to our service(s), product(s) or Website.
  * To allow you to participate in interactive features of our service, when you choose to do so.
  * For internal record keeping.
  * To improve our products, services, and Website.
  * To send promotional emails about new products, special offers or other information which We think you may find interesting using the email address which you have provided.
  * To contact you for market research purposes. We may contact you by email, phone, fax or mail.
  * To customize the Website according to your interests.

We may also use your information, or permit selected third parties to use your information, to contact you about goods and services that may be of interest to you where you have consented to be contacted for such purposes. If you do not want Us to use your information in this way, or to provide your information to third parties for marketing purposes, you may unsubscribe via the included instructions on how to unsubscribe from our mailing list found on the email.

We do not disclose your Personal Information to our advertisers, but We may provide them with Aggregated Data (for example, We may report to them that 500 men aged under the age of 35 clicked on their advertisement on a given day). We may also use Aggregated Data to help advertisers reach the kind of audience they want to target. We may make use of the Personal Information We have collected to enable Us to deliver targeted advertising content. Even though We only disclose Aggregated Data that is not personally-identifiable to advertisers without your consent, when you click on or otherwise interact with an advertisement, there is a possibility that the advertiser may assume that you meet the target criteria they selected. We make no representation or warranty regarding the privacy policies of any advertisers or other web pages you may reach by clicking on any advertisement found on the Website.

## Disclosure of Your Personal Information

We may disclose Personal Information that you provide via this Website to the following third parties:

  * Any of Our subsidiaries and affiliates.
  * Contractors and service providers We use to support our business, including any third parties who support the Website or the provision of products and services to you. 
  * In the event of merger, acquisition, or any form of sale of some or all of the Company’s assets, including any form of insolvency proceeding or bankruptcy, or as part of a corporate reorganization, stock sale, or change in control in which case Personal Information held by Us may be among the assets transferred to the buyer. In such a case, the Transferee or recipient of Personal Information will be bound to these terms. 
  * With your consent.

We may also disclose your personal information to third parties to: Comply with any (a) court order, or lawfully issued subpoena, (b) request from state, local, or federal law enforcement, (c) to investigate suspected fraud, harassment or other violation of law, (d) to investigate any violation of the Website’s Policy,  Terms and Conditions , and other agreements between you and Us, (e) to investigate violations of the rights to third parties, or (f) to investigate any suspected conduct which We deem improper or likely to cause harm to Us or any other customer or person, including exchanging information with other companies and organizations for the purposes of fraud protection and credit risk reduction.

## Choices About How We Use and Disclose Your Information

We strive to provide you with choices regarding the personal information you provide to Us. We have created mechanisms to provide you with the following control over your information:

  * Cookies.   You may refuse to accept cookies by activating the appropriate setting on your browser at any time. However, if you select this setting you may be unable to access certain parts and functions of our Website. Unless you have adjusted your browser setting so that it will refuse cookies, our Website will issue cookies when you direct your browser to our Website.
  * Promotional Offers from Third Parties.  If you do not wish Us to share your personal information with unaffiliated or non-agent third parties for promotional purposes, you can opt-out by adjusting your user preferences in your account profile by checking or unchecking the relevant boxes or by sending Us an e-mail stating your request to  [[email protected]](https://web.archive.org/cdn-cgi/l/email-protection)  . 
  * Promotional Offers from the Company.  If you do not wish to have your e-mail address used for promotional purposes by the Company, you can opt-out by emailing your request to  [[email protected]](https://web.archive.org/cdn-cgi/l/email-protection)   with the subject line “OPT OUT.” You can also always opt-out of receiving e-mail information from Us other than the e-mail informing you of the completion of user registration, correction of user data, or change of password by logging into the Website and adjusting your user preferences in your account profile by checking or unchecking the relevant boxes or by sending Us an e-mail stating your request to  [[email protected]](https://web.archive.org/cdn-cgi/l/email-protection) .   If We have sent you a promotional e-mail, you may send Us a return e-mail asking to be omitted from future e-mail distributions. This opt out does not apply to information provided to the Company as a result of the purchase of a product or service, warranty registration, product service experience or other transactions. 
  * If you provide your email address for the purposes of any promotion, We will use your email address to send you announcements, special offers from Us and our promotional partners, only. Each such email will include instructions on how to unsubscribe from our mailing list.
  * If you refer a friend to our Website or for any product or service We provide, We will ask you for that friend’s name and email address. We will automatically send that friend a one-time email inviting them to visit the Website. That email will also provide your friend with the ability to ask Us to remove his or her information from Our database. Unless removal is requested, We will store that information provided by you for internal tracking purposes. 
  * Personalized Advertising.  If you do not want Us to use Personal Information that we gather to allow third parties to personalize advertisements We display to you, you can opt-out by adjusting your user advertising preferences accordingly in your account profile by checking or unchecking the relevant boxes or by sending Us an e-mail stating your request to  [[email protected]](https://web.archive.org/cdn-cgi/l/email-protection) . If We update this Policy, your continued use of the Website (following the posting of the revised Policy) means that you consent and agree to the terms of the revised Privacy Policy.
  * Links to Third Parties.  The Website may include  links to third-party web sites. The policies and procedures we described here may not apply to third-party sites. Any links from the Website do not imply that the Company endorses or has reviewed the third-party sites. We suggest contacting those sites directly for information on their privacy policies.
  * We may from time to time contract with third party vendors to provide ads to our customers on our behalf via the Internet or to send direct mail to customers whom we think may be interested in our products or services. In order to do so, such vendor may collect anonymous information about your visits to our website using a “cookie”. A cookie is a small piece of data that is sent to your browser or mobile device by websites, mobile apps, and advertisements that you access or use. This data is stored on your browser or mobile device and helps websites and mobile apps to remember things about you to improve your experience with the website. Third-party vendors may then pool the anonymous information that they collect from our website with other sources of information, which may include your name and mailing address, for purposes of determining whether you might be interested in receiving direct mail. If you do not wish for cookies to be placed on your computer, most web browsers permit you to prevent that from taking place. However, please keep in mind that these technologies are an important part of how the website works; removing, rejecting or limiting the use of cookies or other similar technologies might affect the availability and functionality of the website. To opt-out of receiving our direct mail, you may send us an email at [[email protected]](https://web.archive.org/cdn-cgi/l/email-protection)

## Accessing and Correcting Your Personal Information

You can review and update your Personal Information by logging into the Website and visiting your account profile page and making and saving changes. If you have forgotten your password, you can click on the “Forgot your password?” link on the Website to reach a page on which you can submit your e-mail address. Your user name and password then will be e-mailed to you.

You may also send Us an e-mail at  [[email protected]](https://web.archive.org/cdn-cgi/l/email-protection)  to request access to, correct or delete any personal information that you have provided to us. We cannot delete your personal information except by also deleting your user account.

## Your California Privacy Rights

California Civil Code Section § 1798.83 permits users of our Website that are California residents to request certain information regarding our disclosure of personal information to third parties for their direct marketing purposes. To make such a request, please send an e-mail to  [[email protected]](https://web.archive.org/cdn-cgi/l/email-protection) . 

## Data Security

We have implemented commercially reasonable measures designed to secure your Personal Information from accidental loss and from unauthorized access, use, alteration and disclosure. Any payment transactions will be encrypted using SSL technology which encrypts transmitted information. Only employees and third parties who need access to this information in order to perform their duties have access to Financial Information.

The safety and security of your information also depends on you. Where We have given you (or where you have chosen) a password for access to certain parts of our Website, you are responsible for keeping this password confidential. You should not share your password with anyone. We urge you to be careful about giving out information in public areas of the Website like message boards. The information you share in public areas may be viewed by anyone, and may allow anyone to have access to your Personal Information. If you believe your password has been compromised or stolen, you should reset the password on the Website immediately and review your financial records for any incorrect charges.

Unfortunately, the transmission of information via the internet is not completely secure. Although we do our best to protect your personal information, we cannot warrant or guarantee the security of your personal information transmitted to our Website. Any transmission of information, including Personal Information by you to Us is at your own risk.

Although we have implemented commercially reasonable measures to prevent unauthorized access to the Website and Personal Information, the Company will not be liable for actual damages, consequential damages, or special damages due to unauthorized disclosures of Personal Information due to errors in transmission or unauthorized acts of third parties. 

IF YOU DO NOT AGREE TO THIS WAIVER OF RIGHT TO PURSUE AN AWARD OF DAMAGES AGAINST THE COMPANY, YOU MAY NOT ACCESS OR OTHERWISE USE THIS WEBSITE. YOUR CONTINUED USE OF THIS WEBSITE INDICATES YOUR ASSET TO THIS WAIVER.

## Children Under the Age of 13

Our Website is not intended for persons under 13 years of age.  If you are under the age of 13 you are not authorized to use the Website. No person under age 13 may provide any Personal Information to or on the Website. We do not knowingly collect Personal Information from persons under 13. If you are under 13, please do not register on the Website, make any purchases through the Website or send any information about yourself to Us, including your name, address, telephone number or e-mail address. In the event that We learn that We have collected Personal Information from a person under age 13 without verification of parental consent, We will use all reasonable efforts to remove Personal Information related to persons under 13 from our database. If you believe that We might have any information from or about a child under 13, please contact Us at  [[email protected]](https://web.archive.org/cdn-cgi/l/email-protection)

This Website and the Company’s offers, products and services are only available to persons over the age of 18. If you are under 18, you may use the Website, and the Company’s offers, products and services only with the involvement and consent of a parent or guardian. 

## Consent to import of data to the United States of America

This Website is maintained and operated in the United States of America. By using the Website you authorize the storage of Personal Information in the United States.

## Changes to Our Privacy Policy

This Policy may change from time to time, and your continued use of the Website is deemed to be acceptance of such changes, so please check this Policy periodically for updates. It is our policy to post any changes we make to our Policy on this page, and to conspicuously notify you of our changes on the Website. By continuing to use the Website, you consent and agree to be bound to the Policy as it may be updated. 

If you have questions regarding this Policy, please contact Us at:

Boxy Charm, Inc.,  
880 SW 145th AVE  
Pembroke Pines, FL, 33027  
305-705-3752  
[[email protected]](https://web.archive.org/cdn-cgi/l/email-protection)

The date the Policy was last revised is identified at the top of the page.

6482062-1
